<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Github repos on A Test Site</title>
    <link>https://sarathbabu.github.io/github/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Github repos on A Test Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://sarathbabu.github.io/github/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Icons Generator</title>
      <link>https://sarathbabu.github.io/github/androidiconsgenerator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sarathbabu.github.io/github/androidiconsgenerator/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A simple python script to genearte the generic icons for android applications. You don&amp;rsquo;t need any online application and downloding of archives and extraction. You can simply use this script to generate icons fron PNG images with which ever size (dpi value) you need and the color you like. You can also specify padding on the icon (dpi value) if you want. All you are left to do is simple copy paste the drawable folders into the project directory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just think how many times you need to change the size and/or color of icons in your application while development. If you depend on an online application it will be a boring task of uploading and downloading and extracting.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Android</title>
      <link>https://sarathbabu.github.io/github/easyandroid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sarathbabu.github.io/github/easyandroid/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This android library will lessen your soding efforts to do SQLite database migration, Requesting runtime pemission on devices with Android operating system following Lollipop, Runtime tracking the netwok status change. All these are usual coding requirements in an Android application development, it true that we all are already femiliar with these operations an wrote code manytime for these operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My effort is to make these functionalities(and many others in future) into a single resusable package which can be easily interated into the applications.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>